import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const kingLandData: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "What is the main setting of 'King the Land'?",
    options: [
      "A royal palace",
      "A modern city",
      "A historical kingdom",
      "A luxury resort",
    ],
    answer: "A luxury resort",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the main male character in 'King the Land'?",
    options: ["Lee Seong-ju", "Choi Jae-hyun", "Jang Min-ho", "Kim Jin-woo"],
    answer: "Lee Seong-ju",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the profession of the main female character, who plays a significant role in the series?",
    options: ["Hotelier", "Chef", "Actress", "Businesswoman"],
    answer: "Hotelier",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character is known for their ambitious plans to improve the resort?",
    options: ["Lee Seong-ju", "Jang Min-ho", "Choi Jae-hyun", "Kim Jin-woo"],
    answer: "Lee Seong-ju",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What challenge does the main female character face at the beginning of the series?",
    options: [
      "Personal debt",
      "Family scandal",
      "Job insecurity",
      "Romantic entanglements",
    ],
    answer: "Job insecurity",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the luxury resort featured prominently in the series?",
    options: ["King's Haven", "Royal Retreat", "King's Resort", "Palace Hotel"],
    answer: "King's Resort",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Lee Seong-ju's rival in the series?",
    options: ["Jang Min-ho", "Choi Jae-hyun", "Kim Jin-woo", "Park Hyun-sik"],
    answer: "Jang Min-ho",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary focus of the series' plot?",
    options: [
      "Corporate intrigue",
      "Family drama",
      "Romantic relationships",
      "Historical events",
    ],
    answer: "Corporate intrigue",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What personal quality is Lee Seong-ju known for in his approach to managing the resort?",
    options: ["Charisma", "Persistence", "Innovation", "Diplomacy"],
    answer: "Innovation",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character provides significant support to Lee Seong-ju throughout the series?",
    options: ["Choi Jae-hyun", "Jang Min-ho", "Kim Jin-woo", "Seo Ji-hye"],
    answer: "Choi Jae-hyun",
  },
];
